{
    "id": "a42217841a4849da95cd7ebf62f03269",
    "title": "Other, Another And Others",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Can I have …………………… piece of cake?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "another",
                "other",
                "others"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "baa8a4cb193d420bad7920dadb6f1dbf"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has bought ………………… car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "another",
                "other"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5a4cde22835143659d9ecea650aeae7a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you got any ………………….. ice creams?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5a7eaca990f34fa48136032ce28c8f0a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She never thinks about ………………….. people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "another",
                "other"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "da09d1c03ff447fd9e6c4edc5defe9c3"
        },
        {
            "question": "They love each ………………… very much.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "085e365d25aa4f48b6b393a2120624d3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where are the ……………………… boys?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "697948ee10ef481badd8ded73e45370c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He never thinks of …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another",
                "others"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e77bfe494a434a6588c3fe866bfb62b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "We will be staying for …………………… few weeks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "another",
                "other",
                "others"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4d229d4b2c0d45b8bf6b9442770fa347"
        },
        {
            "question": "They sat for hours looking into one ………………… eyes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "other's",
                "another's"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "98f6e0b8c1d04c288633c360d9e435cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "They talk to each ………………… a lot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "others",
                "another's"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a1a8e815f21c4d35a908dcf84b5df062"
        }
    ]
}